ERICK GARCIA



CONTACT

@ erickgarciap779@gmail.com

Github.com/erickdevup

erickdevup.netlify.app

in LinkedIn.com/in/erickdevup

★ Twitter.com/erickdevup

SKILLS

Html

Css

Javascript

ReactJs

NextJs

NodeJs

TailwindCss

ChakraUI

Sass

Git/Github

EXPERIENCE

BuildPayLink

15/9/2022 - 25/12/2022

Web Developer

Self-hosted open source project, collaborating with a small team, making major contributions, on server-side rendering, working with database, apis creation and consumption, frontend customization, technical SEO, login and registration.

technology: nextjs,next-seo ,swr, sglite, sass, Rest api.

HSort

22/1/2023 - Present

Web Developer

short form video social network prototype (ex:tiktok), for the hive blockchain, using NextJs, css Modules, SSR, connection to the blockchain, work with the video api.

Erickdevup

16/3/2023 - present

Frontend Web Developer React

I have been working as a contract in various blockchain projects as Frontend Developer NextJs / Chakraui in which I have interacted with API, performed form validation, created KYC processes with document and identity validation.

EDUCATION

MiduDev

Course Frontend Developer React

In this course I learned a lot about ReactJs: jsx, hooks, context, custom hooks, react rooter... I have put everything I learned into practice in my projects

MiduDev

Course Web Developer Nextjs

Un curso de Next.js te enseñaría a desarrollar aplicaciones web utilizando React y Node.js en el lado del servidor, lo que te permitiría crear aplicaciones web escalables y de alta calidad.

ABOUT ME

Hello, my name is Erick García, I'm 21 years old, I can quickly adapt to new challenges and technologies. I am really passionate about my job as a developer and I am constantly looking for ways to improve my skills and learn new technologies. I have a problem solving mindset and am always looking for ways to provide the best possible solution for every project I work on.